[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the properties of gold?", "correct_answer": "It is unaffected by air and moisture", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "It is chemically inert", "It dissolves in nitric acid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Eric Dravens war paint in The Crow is stylized to look like the mask he and Shelly used to play with together.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which ingredient for bread hurts the leavening (rising) ability?", "correct_answer": "salt", "incorrect_answers": ["water", "flour", "sugar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the following is not a Japanese ghost or spirit?", "correct_answer": "ekimmu", "incorrect_answers": ["zashiki-warashi", "mujina", "ubume"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie My Girl, what was Thomas J. looking for in the woods when he died from an allergic reaction to bee stings?", "correct_answer": "Vadas ring", "incorrect_answers": ["his bike", "Vadas bike", "his glasses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most commonly used word for yogurt in India, as the word yogurt is unknown there?", "correct_answer": "Dahi", "incorrect_answers": ["Rakhi", "Kameishi", "Majereshi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the study of memory, what does the term mnemonist refer to?", "correct_answer": "Individual with exceptional memory", "incorrect_answers": ["Individual with severe memory disorders", "Individual who tends to create false memories", "Individual who has recovered from amnesia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the head of the United Nations called?", "correct_answer": "Secretary General", "incorrect_answers": ["General Commissioner", "UN General", "President General"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chet Ripley", "correct_answer": "The Great Outdoors", "incorrect_answers": ["Weird Science", "Nate and Hayes", "Uncle Buck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is true about ants diet?", "correct_answer": "Most ants are omnivores.", "incorrect_answers": ["All ants are herbivores.", "All ants are carnivores.", "Most ant species are carnivores."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The common name of the tendo calcaneus or calcaneal tendon of the human body was derived from the name of this Greek mythological hero.", "correct_answer": "Achilles", "incorrect_answers": ["Odysseus", "Hercules", "Heracles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film, directed by Robert Flaherty, is considered to be the first documentary film.", "correct_answer": "Nanook of the North", "incorrect_answers": ["Triumph of the Will", "Why We Fight", "White Wilderness"]}]